What are you doing today?
I'm free.
And what are you doing today?
Let's get around the plan.
We'll just keep it on the line and tell each other that we like each other, that we love each other, that we love each other with our voices, and that we can fight for what we want.
This is YASUMOTO Ayaka's question-and-answer segment.
Yay!
Okay, so...
I'm not going to answer the "where am I?" question.
I'm not going to answer questions about where we are, but I'd like to answer some of the questions we've asked on the Insta page.
First of all, I'm going to sit down.
What is your favorite yakiniku menu?
I know it's not very appropriate.
It's really not appropriate.
My favorite menu item is...
Recently, I like "Senba Sashimi".
It's a menu item that is not grilled.
Go on.
I might as well answer with a gun.
I don't know what to do.
What is in front of me now?
What we have in front of us right now...
The ocean.
Next...
What is your favorite Nagoya steamed dish?
Nagoya steamed chicken wings, hands down.
The one with dumplings in the wings.
All the members of EBICHU love that one!
How can I get the same hair color as Aya's?
My hair color this time is orange brown.
It's orange brown!
Next time: orange-brown!
When did you start using Kansai dialect?
I like dialects, not just Kansai dialect.
I speak the language of various prefectures. Ota is Kansai dialect. I speak the Kansai dialect, like "I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
I also use the Kansai dialect in my instagram stories. He uses "oru" and "oru" a lot.
What kind of sunscreen do you use? I just got it.
It's this one from Biore. It's so sticky.
I don't know what type it is. It's almost like water. It's a sunscreen that's like a lotion...like a lotion.
It's very smooth. You don't feel like you're applying it, so I highly recommend it to everyone.
Are you an early riser? I'm pretty good at this.
I recommend it.
I'm the type of person who doesn't fidget in bed.
If my brain says, "I'll be up soon," my brain says, "I'll be up soon," so I might not fall back to sleep.
I might not sleep twice at all.
What kind of food do you eat when you don't have an appetite?
I think it's a hot day, like today, it's almost 30 degrees Celsius, but I eat even if I don't have an appetite.
What do you eat even if you don't have an appetite?
I love cold soba noodles.
I eat soba no matter how I feel in summer.
This is pretty common, isn't it?
Is this your MVTI?
I've probably done this once.
I wonder what it was.
Like with President Obama.
With Woody.
With Woody?
And the guy rolling the camera.
What was it?
I'll have him look it up and pop it in.
What's that?But I'm glad I like Uttei.
But I like Uttei, so I'm glad.
What do you wear when it's hot?
Today, I want to be a zenra.
Oh, this... this... this...
What's the best compliment you've ever received?
This one.
Like, what's the nicest thing someone's said to you recently?
We've been talking about it.
It's pretty difficult, isn't it?
But I answered...
I'm a genius?
It makes me happy to be told I'm a genius.
But isn't it a pretty godlike thing to be told you're a genius? And then I thought...
I decided not to do it.
I wonder what makes you happy. It's the compliment that makes me the happiest.
But I think my ideal adult or woman is...
Someone who has her own ideas and can clearly express them.
I admire people who can clearly express their thoughts.
I don't know.
When someone says something like, "You're a person who has her own opinions.
I feel happy that I'm getting closer to the person I admire.
Someone sent me a message saying, "Lucky human, lucky human.
What do you mean? Is that him or that Kaho guy?
Are there any supplements you take on a regular basis?
Do you know what it is? It's called "Ni Ni".
It boosts the body's immune system and removes toxins.
There's something called "noni" that's all-purpose and leads to good health, and I think noni juice was popular for a while.
I've been trying to take a supplement type of it for my health.
My skin hasn't been feeling so good the past few days, what is the first thing I should do when that happens?
This depends on what kind of skin care routine the person is following.
For those who have not taken care of their skin at all
If you have not taken care of your skin at all, please start by washing your face thoroughly and using a lotion and cream at the very least.
I usually do a lot of basic things.
If you like beauty and other things, please stop all of them and start from the beginning.
I'd like you to stop all of that and start with the very basics.
I'd like you to start with the very basic ones.
Astragalus root lotion.
It's cheap and good.
You can use a very basic lotion.
Don't apply too much.
Just dab it on once or twice.
You can use a very simple Nivea blue kan or something like that.
You can also use a very simple cream like Nivea Aokan.
I think if you change to a simple skin care regimen like that, you can cure your skin problems.
The other day, when Kamo-chan was suffering from rough skin, I told her how to do it.
I showed her how to do it and told her she should keep it simple.
Her skin is getting better little by little.
But applying too much lotion isn't good for the skin either.
In fact, it makes the skin too thin.
The skin is softened by the fact that only one layer of skin should be peeled off during the town over period.
But, in fact, too much lotion is not so good for the skin, and in fact, it makes the skin too soft, so that only one layer of skin, which is supposed to be removed by town over, is removed.
This can also weaken the skin, so too much lotion may not be a good thing.
So it is important to change to very simple products once skin problems occur.
Oh, let's try this.
What kind of child were you when you were little, Aya?
What kind of child were you when you were a little girl?
What was she like as a child? She was very shy. When she was at home, she was the boss, but the moment she went outside, she didn't speak.
He didn't have many friends and was very shy.
Is there any product that can make acne art disappear?
I think vitamin C derivative is very effective for acne art.I think vitamin C derivative is very effective for acne.
I can't say whether this product is good or not, because it depends on the constitution of each person's skin.
I can't say for sure.
I can't say for sure if this product is good or not, but I can say that it is a good, inexpensive vitamin C product.
I can't say for sure, but I would recommend a serum containing a vitamin C derivative, as it is cheap.
I think it will heal very nicely if you apply it to a part of your skin like you would apply medicine for acne.
Please give it a try!
That's all for this corner of Aika Yasumoto's question-and-answer session.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Please subscribe to our channel & give us a good button♡♡!
You and yourself too.
Oh, because I'm lanky just to have met you here and now.
More than that is just affection.
So I can hang on just a little bit longer.
Let's say that one word together.
I'm not ashamed. I'd rather say it.
I love you.
So, what are you doing today?
I'm free.
What are you doing today?
Maybe we can strategize.
Come see me tomorrow.